{
    "id": "ce6913b3f0b54d039dab5859e7fffd27",
    "title": "Prepositions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "See you ……………………………… next Monday.",
            "description": "Prepositions are usually dropped before expressions like next Monday or last Monday. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in",
                "No preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6488848170e449dbcca3b5f29f23552"
        },
        {
            "question": "We entered …………………………… the church.",
            "description": "No preposition is used after enter.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "into",
                "No preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b00475a586134cc09279a1b4301df6e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… what time does the train arrive?",
            "description": "Prepositions are usually omitted before what time...?",
            "answers": [
                "At",
                "In",
                "On",
                "No preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "7e57bea9291b47939a25c0ef444edbdf"
        },
        {
            "question": "One Mr. Samuel is ……………………………….. the phone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1d5ec402f358485da4487d7af3d3bba3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have read almost every novel ……………………………….. Dickens.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "by",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "43c729334d4d40d5a16896a43ac89ff6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She hails ………………………….. a small town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "237631263a644c88abe163c64bbfe950"
        },
        {
            "question": "He belongs …………………………… the local football club.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c8879c9ca0cb4ab9b75f04947b3d5a3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to the market …………………………… my brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d1a8beceb44140a9b4ed0e1beefbe03b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are responsible …………………………………. your actions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dcee94c822b94716ad142fa208ede04e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please fill in the form ………………………….. ink.",
            "description": "We say in ink.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4a98000d2aef4426a8ff4896f9993ee2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She stood ………………………….. him.",
            "description": "Beside means by the side of besides means in addition to.",
            "answers": [
                "beside",
                "besides"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e932fbc9fc88461eb42ab0f15f3ed7b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He decided to quit his job ……………………………… several reasons.",
            "description": "for... reasons....",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "95b66e698bfe444c9aba4cdc06ed59c3"
        }
    ]
}